{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Which of the following immune cells would have an especially low count in a patient with advanced AIDS?", "opta": "Killer T lymphocytes", "optb": "Helper T lymphocyte", "optc": "B lymphocytes", "optd": "None of these", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In cellular immunity, T lymphocytes are responsible for the recognition and killing of foreign invaders. The cells are", "opta": "cytotoxic T lymphocytes (CTL)", "optb": "killer T cells", "optc": "both (a) and (b)", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Plasma cells produce thousands of __________ that are released into the bloodstream", "opta": "antigens", "optb": "antibodies", "optc": "helper T cells", "optd": "virus fragments", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If a person is vaccinated against a disease sometime in the past, which of the following is currently in your body?", "opta": "The disease organism itself and antigens for the disease organism", "optb": "A very high level of antibodies against the disease antigens", "optc": "Memory B lymphocytes for the antigen of this disease organism", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is a protein produced by host cells infected by viruses?", "opta": "Interferon", "optb": "Histamine", "optc": "Antiserum", "optd": "Vaccine", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Polysaccharides on the surface of infecting microorganisms can also activate complement directly in the absence of", "opta": "antibody via the alternative pathway", "optb": "antigen via the alternative pathway", "optc": "antibody via metabolic pathway", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Antibodies bound to an invading microorganism activate the complement system via", "opta": "classical pathway", "optb": "metabolic pathway", "optc": "Embden Meyerhof pathway", "optd": "Entner-Doudoroff pathway", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The immune response to a booster vaccine is called a(n)", "opta": "cellular response", "optb": "innate response", "optc": "primary response", "optd": "secondary response", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Immunological memory is due to", "opta": "short lived macrophage that can recognize specific pathogens", "optb": "long lived B cells that secrete a specific antibody", "optc": "long lived B cells that secrete a specific antigen", "optd": "short lived helper T cells that signal macrophage to divide", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the result of an abnormal response of the immune system to part of a person's own body?", "opta": "Passive immunity", "optb": "Cancer", "optc": "An allergic response", "optd": "An autoimmune disease", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What are the solutions prepared from weakened or dead microorganisms, viruses, or toxins that provide some immunity from diseases?", "opta": "Vaccines", "optb": "Histamines", "optc": "Drugs", "optd": "Antibiotics", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "During exposure to a foreign invader, there are more __________ present in the vertebrate body than before exposure", "opta": "antibodies", "optb": "lymphocytes", "optc": "macrophages and antigens", "optd": "all of these", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To elicit the best antibodies to mouse MHC I, it should be injected into a", "opta": "goat", "optb": "mouse of the same genetic background (strain)", "optc": "mouse of a different strain", "optd": "rat", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To detect a humoral immune response to influenza virus, it is possible to measure", "opta": "cytotoxicity of virus-infected cells in tissue culture", "optb": "dividing T cells in the draining lymph nodes", "optc": "plasma cytokine levels", "optd": "serum antibody titer", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is in the lymph nodes of a person battling a cold virus?", "opta": "Huge numbers of white blood cells", "optb": "Trapped viruses that have been roaming the body", "optc": "Lymph ducts that enter and exit the nodes and Lymph fluid", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Immunogenicity", "opta": "depends on the ability of the native antigen to be presented by MHC", "optb": "is usually a property of self antigens such as eye tissue", "optc": "is not a property of antibodies", "optd": "is not a property of haptens", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}